Shakira, we're ready
夏奇拉，我们准备好了
We're ready
我们准备好了
We're ready, too
我们也准备好了
Oh-eh-oh-eh, eh-oh-eh
You knew from the day you were born
从出生那天起你就知道
That here in this place you belong
这里，就是你归属的地方
You been this brave all along
你一直都这样勇敢
What broke you once made you strong
曾经击垮你的，让你更强大
Dai, dai, iko
加油，加油，走吧
Dale, allez, let's go
上吧，冲啊，我们走
Dai, dai, iko
加油，加油，走吧
Dale, allez, let's go
上吧，冲啊，我们走
Come follow your desire
追随你心中的渴望
Where there's a will, there's a way
有志者，事竟成
You are the owner of that fire
那团火焰，属于你
No one can take it away
没人能将它夺走
Sweat and blood to write your story
用汗水与热血，书写你的故事
That is how you paved the way
你就是这样，铺就前路
You're about to reach the glory
你即将抵达荣耀
Only one step away
只差一步之遥
All the highs and lows
所有的起起落落
All the tears and the pain
所有的泪水与伤痛
You been there through it all, been through it all
你都一一挺了过来，全都挺了过来
Just do it again
再来一次就好
Now you got to believe (I believe)
现在你要相信（我相信）
'Cause you know what it takes
因为你深知这需要什么
To be living my dream
才能活成我梦想的模样
At the top of your game
站上你的巅峰
Feel it, got everything you needed
去感受，你需要的一切都已具备
Now bring it like you mean it
现在全力以赴，拿出真本事
Just like you mean it
拿出你全部的真心
Dale, no olvides lo que vales
加油，别忘了你的价值
Juega como tú sabes
用你最拿手的方式去踢
Como tú sabes
就像你最擅长的那样
Energy is contagious, you know
你知道，能量是会传染的
And it never fails
而且屡试不爽
No, no
不，不
No one's getting tired
没有人会疲惫
I know
我知道
'Cause you got that fire
因为你心怀那团火
Hey-oh
Dream a little higher
把梦想，再放高一点
Let's go, let's go, let's go
走起，走起，走起
Hey-oh
We've taken all that our hearts can hold
我们已承载了心所能容的一切
We can't hold on to the past no more
我们不能再紧抓着过去不放
From the dirt and the tears, we make gold
从尘土与泪水中，我们炼出黄金
We are more than flesh and bones
我们远不只是血肉之躯
All the highs and lows (Highs and lows)
所有的起起落落（起起落落）
All the tears and the pain
所有的泪水与伤痛
You been there through it all, been through it all
你都一一挺了过来，全都挺了过来
Just do it again
再来一次就好
Now you got to believe (I believe)
现在你要相信（我相信）
'Cause you know what it takes
因为你深知这需要什么
To be living my dream
才能活成我梦想的模样
At the top of your game
站上你的巅峰
Feel it, got everything you needed
去感受，你需要的一切都已具备
Now bring it like you mean it
现在全力以赴，拿出真本事
Just like you mean it
拿出你全部的真心
Dale, no olvides lo que vales
加油，别忘了你的价值
Juega como tú sabes
用你最拿手的方式去踢
Como tú sabes
就像你最擅长的那样
Pelé, Maradona, Maldini, Romário
贝利、马拉多纳、马尔蒂尼、罗马里奥
Cristiano Ronaldo
克里斯蒂亚诺·罗纳尔多
El Pibe, Iniesta, Beckham y Kaká
巴尔德拉马、伊涅斯塔、贝克汉姆和卡卡
Messi, Mbappé, Salah
梅西、姆巴佩、萨拉赫
Brazil, Uruguay, Argentina, Colombia
巴西、乌拉圭、阿根廷、哥伦比亚
US, England, Germany, France
美国、英格兰、德国、法国
South Africa, España, México, Japan
南非、西班牙、墨西哥、日本
Korea, Netherlands
韩国、荷兰
Oh-eh-oh-eh, eh-oh-eh
You knew from the day you were born
从出生那天起你就知道
That here in this place you belong
这里，就是你归属的地方
You been this brave all along
你一直都这样勇敢
What broke you once made you strong
曾经击垮你的，让你更强大
Dai, dai, iko
加油，加油，走吧
Dale, allez, let's go
上吧，冲啊，我们走
Dai, dai, iko
加油，加油，走吧
Dale, allez, let's go
上吧，冲啊，我们走
Dai, dai, iko
加油，加油，走吧
Dale, allez, let's go
上吧，冲啊，我们走
Dai, dai, iko
加油，加油，走吧
Dale, allez, let's go
上吧，冲啊，我们走